Contato

Dublin +353874417340 (Home) ski.fernanda@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fcetnarovski (LinkedIn)

www.cocktailf.com (Company) www.behance.net/fcentarovski (Portfolio)

Principais competências

InDesign Graphic Design YouTube

Languages

French (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

JavaScript: Functions
Web Development Foundations:
Web Technologies

Learning the JavaScript Language
Learning GREP with InDesign
After Effects CC 2015 Essential
Training

Publications

Espaço e Criação Smartbox CV

Fernanda Gabriele Cetnarovski

Database Publishing Specialist at Smartbox Group

Dublin, Leinster, Ireland

Resumo

I'm a Publishing Specialist/Graphic Designer who has recently fallen in love with the automation of things! I'm currently studying javascript and applying it (with the help of some Regular Expressions) for repetitive publishing tasks using adobe indesign - I'm really excited about the results. My goal is to keep learning about automation tools as well as javascript applied to the web.

Experiência

Smartbox Group 2 anos 11 meses

Database Publishing Specialist abril de 2018 - Present (1 ano 11 meses)

County Dublin, Ireland

At Smartbox, we produce a large number of catalogues in several languages to be distributed around Europe. In order to automate the creation of those catalogues — inner pages and packaging — we work with a powerful plug in to Adobe Indesign called EasyCatalog. This tool is capable of automating the creation of an extense catalogue (using Indesign master pages) in only a few minutes. All along with that, we work with Enfocus Switch — our automation software that manages the scripts (in javascript) and the workflow. Switch, EasyCatalog and the javascript for Indesign and Photoshop we are able to fully automate the catalogue creation.

My main tasks include the preparation of templates in Indesign and to configure EasyCatalog to fully generate different types of boxes planned for each batch. Following this task, coding and troubleshooting EasyCatalog are also present activities in my work routine. In order to improve and eventually fix issues, I also edit and develop code in javascript. Good communication with other departments as product marketing and design is also crucial to achieve the results according to the planning.

Desktop Publisher abril de 2017 - abril de 2018 (1 ano 1 mês)

Dublin, Leinster, Ireland

Smartbox Group is the leader in the experience gift market. Being a desktop publisher at this company requires excellent indesign skills, since we're working day-to-day with numerous catalogs across different countries. The main tasks include fast editing extense catalogs, all along with good communication with design team and copyrighters. After the creation of the booklets, my role as a desktop publisher includes pdf exporting and quality check of the files.

YouTube
Youtuber in French linguistics
setembro de 2015 - Present (4 anos 6 meses)
Dublin

CocktailF is my YouTube channel - and my personal project! I love learning about languages and French is definitely my favourite one. To spread all the knowledge I have acquired with my experiences and my linguistic books (and also to meet more people excited about learning French) I run a YouTube channel called CocktailF. In this channel, I try to explain in a fun way the beautiful complications that exist in the French language. As a result, I also give online French tuition to the most enthusiastic subscribers of my channel. In order to run CocktailF I have developed solid video skills: how to set lights for the camera, storytelling techniques, and video editing. I mainly use Adobe Premiere Pro to all the assembling and colour correction on the short movies, but I also work with Adobe After Effects when creating motion graphics and animation. Other than that, this YouTube channel also allows me to have contact with people from different backgrounds trough social media, what also improves my ability in online communication.

Liz McKeon & Associates Book Designer fevereiro de 2015 - abril de 2015 (3 meses) County Dublin, Ireland

This book was created by Liz Mckeon to help salon owners improve their gain and also to learn how to manage their business. It was designed with a simple and clear language, with vivid colours and bidimensional icons.

Portella Idiomas
Teacher of French
setembro de 2012 - janeiro de 2014 (1 ano 5 meses)
Batel, Curitiba/PR

I worked teaching French and English, one to one tuition.

Reflet communication - Agence Digitale Graphic Design Internship fevereiro de 2012 - julho de 2012 (6 meses) Belfort, France

Ad campaign creation, photo retouching and image editing.

Formação acadêmica

Code Institute

Diploma In Software Development, Full Stack Web Development · (2019 - 2020)

Universidade Tecnológica Federal do Paraná Tecnólogo em Design Gráfico, Graphic Design · (2009 - 2013)

Université de Technologie de Belfort-Montbéliard Exchange, Communication, General (2011 - 2012)

Universidade Federal do Paraná
Tecnólogo em Comunicação Institucional, Business/Corporate
Communications · (2009 - 2012)